Seeing is deceiving
Looking Glass is a thriller, mystery film directed by Tim Hunter.
A psycho- sexual thriller following a couple that buys an old motel in the desert looking for a new beginning, but what seemed at first as an
escape is soon a thrilling ride through a mysterious world when Ray discovers a two way mirror and witnesses a horrifying murder.
In a twisted game of cat and mouse, Ray must race to save his wife and himself from a
gruesome secret connected to the motel and the strange people who visit there.
Ray, played by Nicolas Cage.
Maggie, played by Robin Tunney.
Howard, played by Marc Blucas.
Tommy, played by Ernie Lively.
Jessica 'Room 6', played by Jacque Gray.
Ben, played by Bill Bolender.
Looking Glass is a 2018 American thriller film directed by Tim
Hunter and starring Nicolas Cage and Robin Tunney.
It was released in the United States by Momentum Pictures on February 16, 2018.
The film explores themes of motel, dominatrix, swimming pool, murder, voyeurism.
The tone is mind_bending and intense.